UNC COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR

- 919-656-7462
- aszala@cs.unc.edu
- linkedin.com/in/aszala/github.com/aszala
- % <u>aszala.com</u>

ABOUT ME

Seven years of web and application development experience. Many awards at hackathons. Research Assistant at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group).

Strong programming skill in Python, Java, C#, C, JavaScript/NodeJS, and HTML/CSS. Experienced with Machine Learning, AWS, GCP, IBM Cloud, Docker, Unity, Node.JS backend creation, Git/GitHub, Expert certified in Excel.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Major (B.S.)

UNC Chapel Hill Class of 2023

Statistics and Analytics Minor

UNC Chapel Hill Class of 2023

PUBLICATIONS

Research paper titled, "ArraMon: A Joint Navigation-Assembly Instruction Interpretation Task in Dynamic Environments", accepted into EMNLP Findings. https://arxiv.org/abs/2011.07660

COURSEWORK

- Java Programming
- Special Topics in Computer Science
- System Fundamentals
- Data Structures
- Computer Organization
- Models of Languages and Computation
- Calculus I, II, III
- Discrete Mathematics

EXPERIENCE

Summer Intern 2020 (May – August)

Interned at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group) research lab. Developed an AI model to interpret natural language instructions and carry out robotic action tasks. Model was built in Python using PyTorch and a simulation environment was built in Unity with C# and hosted on AWS. Research paper accepted into EMNLP Findings.

Undergraduate Research Assistant 2019 – Present

Researching new ideas and directions for Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Machine Learning at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group). Primarily focused on integrating NLP with other fields of research such as Computer Vision and Embodiment.

TSA President 2018 – 2019 TSA Member 2015 – 2019

Software developer and leader at the school Technology Student Association (TSA). I have won several awards from TSA.

Webmaster 2018 - Present

Created and maintain the following websites using HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript/jQuery. Also familiar with hosting NodeJS backend servers.

- Personal website portfolio <u>aszala.com</u>
- TSA webmaster aszala.com/2019-webmasters

Software/Application Developer 2014 - Present

Developed several games and applications.

- Developed various AI for personal use, hackathons, and research.
- Developed several video games using Unity/C# and Java.
- Developed a NodeJS backend server to work with personal projects.
- Developed various mobile apps for Android and desktop/web apps.